Hello.
こんにちは
You have such a beautiful face.
すごい綺麗な顔だししてね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Her skin is also pure white.
肌も真っ白で
I don't think I have anything to do with this type of shooting.
こういう撮影には全く縁がなさそうだけど
I agree.
そうですね
I have no experience.
経験ないです
How old are you now?
今、年齢は何歳?
My age is 19 years old.
年齢は19歳です
19 years old.
19歳
yes.
はい
Her name is Suzuka-chan, which is cute.
名前も鈴香ちゃんってかわいいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
How many centimeters are you tall?
身長は何センチ?
Height is 160cm.
身長は160センチです
160cm?
160センチか
He's quite tall.
結 構背が高いんだね
It's expensive.
高いです
Isn't he very popular?
すごいモテるんじゃないの?
this.
これ
It's a secret.
内緒です
secret?
内緒?
yes.
はい
You'll know that you'll definitely be popular.
絶対モテるってわかっちゃうよ
How many cups?
カップ数は?
Cup size is D cup.
カップ数はDカップです
I'm a D cup.
Dカップなんだ
I see.
なるほどね
As always, what are you doing?
いつもさ、何をやってるの?
Usually.
普段は
I'm usually a college student, so I go to school.
普段は大学生なので、学校に行ってます
School?
学校か
yes.
はい
I'm taking school seriously.
学 校を真面目に行ってるんだ
I take school seriously.
学校を真面目に行ってます
fun?
楽しい?
It's fun.
楽しいです
That was good.
良かったね
I see you're having a good school life.
いい学校生活を送ってんだね
What do you do on your days off from school?
学校お休みの日は何をやってるの?
On my days off from school, I go to a cafe with my friends and have lunch.
学校お休みの日は、友達とカフェとかに行ってご飯食べてます
What kind of food do you like?
ご飯何好きなの?
The rice is pancakes.
ご飯は、パンケーキです
Pancakes?
パ ンケーキ?
It's so cute.
すげー可愛いね
So, Harajuku or something like that.
じゃあ、原宿とか、そこら辺だね
that's right.
そうです
There are a lot of them around here.
いっぱいあるもんな、そこら辺ね
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏はいるんですか?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏はいません
not here?
いません?
why?
なぜ?
I don't have much experience with men.
あんまり、男性経験がないので
Are you a little wary?
ちょっと警戒心があるのかな?
I feel nervous when talking to my boyfriend.
彼 氏と話すとき、緊張したいんです
That's right.
そうなんだ
Well, I'm really excited today.
じゃあ、今日めちゃめちゃドキドキだね
I'm so excited.
ドキドキです
I was nervous.
緊張したよね
Even her nervous face is so cute.
緊張してる顔もすごい可愛い
What kind of men do you like?
どんな男性が好きなんですか?
After all, I like men who are tolerant.
やっぱり、包容力がある男性が好きです
I see.
なるほど
So, is it better to be bigger?
じゃあ、体は大きい方がいいの?
I prefer someone with a relatively average body.
体は、 割と普通めの人がいいです
It's a matter of the heart, then.
心の問題だね、じゃあ
that's right.
そうです
In terms of appearance?
見た目的には?
I like people who have a refreshing appearance.
見た目は、さわやか系の人が好きです
Is it refreshing?
さわやか系か
Who would be a celebrity?
芸能人だと誰だろう?
As for celebrities, I like Sota Fukunobu and Taishi Nakagawa.
芸能人の方だと、 福信壮太さんとか中川太子さんが好きです
I see.
なるほど ね
It's refreshing.
さわやかだね
It was so refreshing.
すごいさわやかだったわ
I see.
なるほどね
Don't you like older people?
なんか、おじさん系の人は好きじゃない?
I like kind people, even uncle-like people.
おじさん系の人も、 優しい人は好きです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I see.
なるほどね
So, what are you doing now that makes you happy?
じゃあ、今何してる時が幸せですか?
When I'm happy, I feel happy when I buy clothes or something.
幸せの時は、 お洋服とか買ったりする時が 幸せを感じます
Do you like shopping?
買い物好きなの?
I like shopping.
買い物好きです
I see.
そうか
Do you buy things that are quite expensive?
結構高いのも買ったりするの?
I don't really care about the high price.
高いのは、あまり興味がないです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I feel like I really want to be her.
めっちゃ彼女にしたい感じだね
That's great.
それ最高だね
I see.
なるほどね
How many people have experience so far?
今までさ、 経験人数何人?
The number of experienced people is 4 people.
経験人数は、 4人です
There are four of us.
4人なんだ
It looks like there are more of them.
もっと多そうな顔にいるんだ
Surprisingly, it's pretty solid, or rather, it's small.
意外に、 結構堅実というか、 少ないんだね
There aren't many.
少ないです
Are they all boyfriends?
それは全員彼氏?
Some people are not boyfriends.
彼氏じゃない人もいます
Some people don't.
じゃない人もいるんだ
So there are 4 people in total.
それで合計4人なんだね
That's not much.
それは少ないよね
That's right.
そっかそっか
Do any of the four of you have any naughty episodes?
その4人の中で、 エッチなエピソードがあったりする?
I dated someone once, in the car,
1回付き合った人で、 車の中で、
What I did is impressive.
したのが印象的です
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
Was that a little exciting?
それはちょっと興奮したの?
I was excited.
興奮しました
Ahahahaha Were there people around?
あ はははは 周りに人はいたの?
In a parking lot with no one around.
周りに、いや、 誰もいない駐車場とかで
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I did it.
やりました
That's naughty.
エッチだね
Are there any other episodes?
他に何かエピソードある?
Any other episodes?
他にエピソード?
But when I'm alone, I do this.
でも、1人でしちゃうときとか、 こんなにするんだね
Yes, it's so cute.
はーいって、すげーかわいい
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
How do you feel when you're alone?
1人でどういうふうな思いにする?
I have a phone at home, so I used it.
家に電話があるので、 それを使って、
I'm doing it alone.
1人でしてます
How long does that take per week?
それ、週どんぐらいするの?
About 3 times a week.
週、 週3回ぐらい
About 3 times a week?
週3回ぐらい?
Ah, that's normal.
あ、そこは普通なんだね
It would be amazing if it happened every day.
毎日だったらすごかった
As expected.
さすがに
What do you like most about the phone?
電話が一番好きなの?
I like phone calls.
電話は好きです
Why don't you use the one you put in?
入れるやつは使わないの?
I only put it in once in a while.
入れるやつは、 たまに
I'm sure you're prepared.
一応用意はあるんだね
I can't imagine it from the looks.
見た目からは想像がつかないけど
Well then, I guess you like naughty girls quite a lot.
じゃあもう、エッチな子は結構好きなんだね
I like it.
好きです
I agree.
そうだ ね
From a man's point of view, it's great.
男からしたら最高だね
If there is a girl who is this cute and likes sex,
こんなに可愛くて、エッチ好きな女の子いたら、
I'd almost make it my girlfriend.
彼女にしちゃうくらいだね
So, what about S or M?
じゃあ、 SかMかは?
It's M.
Mです
Mなんだ
How M?
どんぐらいM?
However, in terms of percentage, about 90% are M.
でも、割合で言ったら、 9割ぐらいMです
About 90% M?
9割ぐらいM?
It's worth bullying.
いじめがいがあるな
That's right.
そうなんだね
Nice, masochistic girls.
いいね、Mな女の子は
What kind of personality do you think you have?
自分の性格はどういう性格だと思う?
However, I think I'm quite shy.
でも、結構恥ずかしがりやと思います
I see.
なるほどね
yes.
はい
You've done your best.
それなりと頑張ってきてくれたね
thank you.
ありがとう
Well, lastly, when was the last time you had sex?
じゃあ、最後はさ、 一番最近、いつエッチしたの?
The most recent one was about 3 months ago.
一番最近だと、 3ヶ月前ぐらいです
It's been open for 3 months.
3ヶ月開いてるんだ
It's a waste.
もったいないね
Is there no such thing as a sex friend?
セフレみたいなのいないの?
I'm not there.
いないです
There are a lot of things like that, like dating, etc.
いっぱいそういう、 付き合ってるとか、
It seems like there are a lot of requests.
要望が多そうだけど
I see.
そうか
なるほどね
Well then, Suzuka-chan.
じゃあ、鈴香ちゃん
yes.
はい
Just stand there for a moment.
ちょっとそこ、立ってみて
Your style and face are perfect.
スタイルも顔も完璧だね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Are you embarrassed to be photographed so close?
こんな近くで撮られて、恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
後
Please see ro.
ろ を見てください
Regarding your body, where is your favorite place?
自分の体ですが、 好きな場所はどこですか?
My favorite place is the neck.
好 きな場所は、 首レです
Neck.
首レ
It's hidden now.
今隠されちゃってるもんね
What about your butt?
お尻とかは?
I think it's pretty good.
結構、いいと思います
Is it crisp?
プリッとしてる?
yes.
はい
It's time to try rolling it.
そろそろ巻くってみしてみてよ
That's such a beautiful butt.
すげー綺麗なお尻だね
Only 4 people have eaten this so far.
これまだ4人しか食べてないんだわ
Look back at me and see only my face.
こっち振り返ってみて、顔だけ
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗だな
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Turn this way.
こっち向いちゃって
Okay, wear a skirt too.
いいよ、スカートもしちゃって
Kuro-chan, come here.
黒ちゃん、ここ来て
Suzuka-chan.
鈴香ちゃん
This is Kuro-chan.
これ、黒ちゃんです
please.
お願いします
copper?
どう?
Who is this fifth person?
この5人目の相手は?
I'm so excited.
ドキドキします
Are you excited?
ドキドキする?
You look so perverted, don't you?
すげー変態そうな顔してるでしょ
Kuro-chan, please take this off and put it on.
黒ちゃん、これ着外してあげて
Take off your clothes.
それ服脱いで
The style is really nice too.
スタイルもめちゃくちゃいいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Shape your breasts.
おっぱいの形えろ
This is idol class.
これはアイドル級ですわ
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
It really has an amazing neck.
本当に首レすごいね
My waist is tight.
ウエストがキュッてしまってるわ
Look this way.
こっち向いて
That's a really beautiful body.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗な体だな
Shall I take off that bra?
それブラ取っちゃおうか
Those are really beautiful breasts.
すげー綺麗なおっぱいだね
People say you have a pretty shape, right?
形きれいって言われるでしょ?
It is said.
言われます
You'll do it, right?
やるでしょ?
It was so cute.
すごいキュッて
What about Kuro-chan?
黒ちゃんどう?
This boobs.
このおっぱい
Looks great.
最高そう
That's great.
最高だよね
I'm 19 years old.
19歳よ
It's a beautiful body
綺麗な体だ
hey.
ね
Would you like me to come closer and touch it?
近 づいて触ってもらおうか
May I?
いいですか?
yes.
はい
soft?
柔らかい?
What are you doing now?
今何されてる?
I'm being touched.
触られてます
where?
どこ?
chest.
胸
Do you like having your breasts touched?
おっぱい触られるの好き?
like.
好き
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
Shall I try chewing on your breasts?
おっぱいにチューしてみようか
Kuro-chan, how can you touch my breasts?
黒ちゃんどうおっぱい触られるの?
That's good.
いいっすね
delicious?
美味しい?
Show me your face being licked.
舐められてる顔見せて
It's so beautiful.
すんげー綺麗だよ
Even if you make your pants look like tea bags
パンツをティーバッグみたいにしても
Raou.
ら おう
So I stuck my legs out behind me.
それで 後ろにプリッと足を突き出して
Let me stick it out more
もっと突き出してもらお
cormorant.
う
This is a lot of different things.
め いろいけつだねこれ
Let's do some gymnastics
体操したりしてもらお
cormorant.
う
Spread your legs.
足 広めてほら
Where do you think you are filming now?
今どこ撮ってると思う?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's a pussy, right?
おまんこでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Please come forward with your butt.
お尻もっと前に来て
There are various types of gokegi that grow there.
ゴケギ生えてんのいろいろ
yes.
はい
Try picking this up with your hands.
手で拾ってごらんぞこれ
This is so beautiful.
すんごい綺麗なもんこれ
Let's try the experience.
経験あさそう
It's small.
ちっちゃいね
yes.
はい
People say it's tough, right?
きついって言われるでしょ?
It is said.
言われます
Come earlier.
もっと前おいで
yes.
そう
Take a look at the top.
上に足かけてごらん
Open it.
開いてごらん
Try it from your subordinates as well.
手下からもしてごらん
It's a really embarrassing pose.
めちゃめちゃ恥ずかしいポーズしてる
yes.
はい
You can even see her butthole.
お尻の穴もまで見える
How about it?
どうじゃ?
Please be careful soon.
早く注意してごらん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Please lick it a lot.
いっぱい舐めてごらんよ
What about Suzuka-chan's pussy?
スズカちゃんのマンコどう?
Hey.
ちょい
Try sticking your tongue into her pussy hole.
おマンコの穴にも舌突っ込んでごらん
Stick your tongue in the hole.
穴に舌突っ込んでごらん
Put them all in.
全部入れてごらん
Try putting it all in through your butt hole.
お尻の穴から全部入れてごらん
Have you ever been licked here?
ここ舐められたことある?
do not have.
ない
do not have?
ない?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Lick it all the way down to your chest.
くりまで全部舐めてごらん
Please feel free to lick it as much as you like.
い っぱい気持ちよく舐めてごらん
Suzuka-chan, what's your pose?
ス ズカちゃん、ポーズは?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Can you feel it?
手触ってごらん?
It's been a while since I touched it.
久しぶりに触れてた
long time no see.
久しぶり
Is it getting bigger?
大きくなってる?
big.
大きい
big?
大きい?
Do you like big dicks?
大きいチンチン好き?
like.
好き
Well then, let's take it off.
じゃあそれ脱がしてみようか
Smell it.
匂い嗅いで
Does it smell naughty?
エッチな匂いする?
Yeah.
うん
Crow-chan, try putting it on your face.
クローちゃん、顔につけてごらん
Can I add more to the course?
もっとコースにつけていい?
The sme has gotten bigger.
スメ大きくなっちゃったね
Make yourself feel good.
気持ちよくして
How do you feel when you look at Chin Chin?
チンチン見るとどういう気分になる?
Yeah.
うん
Excited.
興奮する
Are you excited?
興奮しちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Please pay attention to the tip.
先っぽに注意してごらん?
glass, sima,
グラス、シマ、
all.
全部
What about Crow-chan?
ク ローちゃんどう?
That's great, this cute girl.
最高だな、この可愛い子
Being licked.
舐められて
Try it.
食べてみて
Has it gotten more painful?
もっと辛くなってきた?
Yeah.
うん
Let's talk a lot.
いっぱい喋ってあげて
Would you like to hear more of the sound and the image from earlier?
もっと音とさっきの映ってごらん?
Shibo Shibou.
しぼうしぼう
Feet, wide.
足、広い
Would you like to make more noise?
もっと音ただやすってごらん?
Drool all over it.
ヨダリいっぱいつけて
Chinchin, is it delicious?
チンチン、おいしい?
Yeah.
うん
Please squeeze out the spittle.
ツバたらしこしこしてごらん?
I want to get you all wet.
いっぱいぬれぬれにしたいって
It's ticking.
カチカチだね
Even in your mouth.
口の中にいるところだって
It's peron from the tongue.
舌からペロンだって
Crow-chan, hurry up.
クローちゃん、もっと早く
Yeah.
うん
painful?
苦しい?
Yeah.
うん
I think Suzuka-chan should be the one to bully her.
スズカちゃんの方がいじめちゃおうかな
Are you ready for bed?
ベッドいこっか
Suzuka-chan.
スズカちゃん
Can you please lie down there?
そこ横になってもらえる?
Have you ever been licked?
舐められたことある?
Yeah.
うん
claw
クロー
Chan, you made me feel so good.
ちゃん、 たくさん気持ちよくしたんだよ
Yeah.
うん
Suzuka-chan, you're an electric masker, right?
スズカちゃん、電マスケでしょ?
Try it yourself.
自分でやってみて
can?
できる?
Yeah.
うん
Does it feel good there?
そこ気持ちいいの?
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it always like that?
いつもそうやっておないの?
Yeah.
うん
Did you put your finger in it?
指入れたの?
Yeah.
うん
Did you put your finger in it?
指入れたの?
It seems tight.
きつそうなんだよ
tight.
きつい
Make it a pleasant part.
気持ちいいパートにして
Are you going?
いっちゃうの?
I went
いった
Try spreading it out.
ま ま広げてみて
Shall we do this next time?
今度これやっちゃおうか
Have you ever used it?
使ったことある?
this.
これ
do not have.
ない
It's shaped like a chinch, right?
チンチの形してるでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Can I try this?
これ入れてみていい?
Yeah.
うん
It's a tight pussy.
きついやまんこやねん
Can you see how deep it is?
奥まで刺さってるのわかる?
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it tight?
きついでしょ?
Please be surprised and satisfied.
びっくり満たしてね
That's tough, hole.
きついね、穴
Does it feel good?
なんか気持ちいいの?
Yeah.
うん
In the case of four,
4つの場合、
What do you feel like doing?
どう する気がする?
Look here.
こっち見て
Because it's exciting.
気が立てるからね
You feel so good, cunt.
気分よいだね、おまんこ
I feel good and sleep well.
気分よいっしり寝てるよ
Sleep.
眠ろ
I went with my nose.
鼻でいっちゃったのだ
Talk a lot.
いっぱいしゃべって
Yeah.
うん
Just smoke some Chubo chocolate.
ちょっとチュボチョコ吸って
Yeah.
うん
stomach
い
My big dick is talking.
っぱ いチンコがしゃべって
Yeah.
うん
Talk quickly.
早くしゃべって
Did you manage to do it in the end?
結局できた?
Yeah.
うん
Then turn in the opposite direction.
じゃあ反対向きになって
Have your pussy thrown.
おまんこ投げてもらう
Did you touch it by chance?
たまたま触ったの?
delicious?
おいしい?
Do you want to lick it?
舐めたい?
Yeah.
うん
Do you want to put this big dick in it?
このでかいチンジ入れたい?
I want to put it in.
入れたい
Let's put it in, then.
入れてみよっか、じゃあ
Drink it all first and see.
最初は飲みきってほら
Just bring it in yourself.
自分で持って入れてほら
Fill it up.
いっぱい入れて
Where does your pussy feel good?
おまんこどこが気持ちいい?
yeah?
ん?
It stings a little bit
ちょっと 刺さってる
Yo.
よ
Lick it.
舐 めてほら
Can you see it even if you enter?
入っても見える?
Yeah.
うん
Try riding on this again.
もう一回この上乗ってみて
facing backwards.
後ろ向きで
Rub it all over your pussy and see.
いっぱいおまんここすりつけてほら
I think I'll be able to do it safely with my legs this time.
今度は足で無事にしそう
facing backwards.
後ろ向きで
This is so naughty.
すんごいエッチだよ、これ
Move your hips a little more.
も っと腰動かしてほら
Even though I left.
いっちゃったのに
Put it in once and see.
一回入れてほら
Now play the same ball.
今度は同じボールしてほら
I like this.
これ好きだね
Suka-chan, what do you do?
すかちゃん、いろいろするの?
Push it and stick it out as hard as you can.
押して思いっきり突き出して
Shall I let you go all the way?
一番奥までさせてみる?
Yeah.
うん
Tell me your pussy feels good.
おまんこ気持ちいいって言って
My pussy feels so good.
おまんこ気持ちいい
It's full of swirls.
まんじれだらけになってるよ
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Pussy
まんこ
It's coming, isn't it?
き ついでしょ、これ
I don't want one drop left.
一 滴残らせんだし
Susuka-chan, in circles.
すすかちゃん、まんじれで
Because I'm so tired.
ヘタヘタだから
Can you clean it up?
綺麗にしてもらえる?
Susuka-chan, did it feel good?
すすかちゃん、気持ちよかった?
I was nervous, but it felt good.
緊張したけど、気持ちよかったです
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
yes.
はい
It was really cute and really good.
めっちゃ可愛かったし、めっちゃ良かった
Let's hide again.
また隠れてやろうよ
yes.
はい
Well then, thank you very much for today.
じゃあ、今日はありがとうございました
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
Bye-bye, Susuka-chan.
すすかちゃん、バイバイ